DEEPALI MAHALE

Assistant QA Manager

 $\begin{tabular}{ll} deepalimahale 471@gmail.com \\ linked in.com/in/deepali-mahale -7167ab 134 \\ 9403418500 \\ Pune, Maharashtra \\ \end{tabular}$

SUMMARY

Software Test Engineer with 3 years 2-month experience, with multiple project experience. Also coordinated with 74 sales and 2000 Operational members, and developed an End-To-End Insurance and Banking distribution system, and improved the business by 64% compared to an existing system.

Testing skills: | Selenium | Maven | Functional testing | Regression Testing | Banking domain | Integration testing | Test Plans Creation | Test scenarios writing | Test cases writing | Test cases Execution | API testing | Reports generation | QA | WebDriver | Docker | Reporting | CI/CD | Appium | Mobile Testing | Testing | REST Assured | Agile and Waterfall SDLC Methodologies | Insurance domain | Automation Testing | Test Case writing |

Tools: Selenium-Java | Postman | Appium | Jenkins | Postman | Microsoft office | Microsoft teams | Git | Jira | Charles | Azure DevOps |

ACCOMPLISHMENT

- Trained 48 salespeople and 100 operational users for the new and improved system, resulting in 64% increase in productivity
- Collaborated in **BRD development** for 7 CRs, which helped build flawless software
- The management team **appreciated** piloting the Web Script for Business logics tested

WORK EXPERIENCE



Assistant Manager - QA Engineer – Jio Platforms Limited

Dec 2023 – Present

- JioCloud is a Free Cloud storage app for all your PHOTOS, VIDEOS, DOCUMENTS, AUDIO, CONTACTS and MESSAGES. Jio Cloud lets you AUTO BACKUP your content
- Test plans and test Script for JioCloud Web Application.
- Conducted complete Manual and automation testing for Jio Cloud projects having multiple features like Jio Cloud Id, Jio Cloud PC, Jio Cloud Enterprise.
- Have tested it on multiple devices, conducting speed tests, file management, sharing and backup options, you can create board, similar to Google Drive.
- Experience in **Functional**, **Regression**, **UAT** Testing.
- Expertise in developing test scenarios, preparing test data, executing test scripts, linking requirements to testcases, creating bug documentation, and reporting test summary.
- Able to work collaboratively with testers, developers, and other team members in testing complex projects and in the overall enhancement of software product quality.
- Managed multiple Agile projects from initiation to completion, utilizing Scrummethodology and ensuring successful delivery of high-quality products.

- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to define project scope, timelines, and deliverables, ensuring alignment with business objectives.
- Conducted daily stand-up meetings, sprint planning, sprint reviews, and retrospectives to ensure timely delivery of project milestones.
- Utilized project management tools such Azure DevOps to track project progress and manage project tasks.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.



Digital Quality Engineer – QualityKisok Technologies

Dec 2020 - 2022

- Created 9 test plans and test Script for 3 projects.
- Conducted complete Manual and automation testing for 3 projects.
- Planned 6 KT activities for whole team and trained for multiple activities.
- Received 12 Appreciations and recognition for efficient work in less time.
- 17 Business Requirement and specifications were tested and within a year and a half the product project was completed and sales increased by 22% during the pandemic.
- Collaborated with engineers and management teams for Daily stand-up, Scrum meetings and enhanced software efficiency by 79%
- Trained 2 business analysts and 4 test members of the global structure and the constructed system, and increase QA Leadership qualities
- Coordinated with **8 Cross-functional Teams** to troubleshoot and collaborate in defects resolution in the system using Service Now.
- Increased hands-on experience in web testing with Java and Selenium testing
- Documentation of **7 user manuals** was done, which helped the quality assurance team to understand the overall functionality of the system
- Performed user acceptance testing and provided sign-off for 18 Product Release
- Conducted negative tests to enhance software quality by 2%
- Responsible for the design of approximately 700 test cases and about 1,800 test cases to follow up on business cases.
- Understanding of Jenkins, Docker, CI, Postman, Testng, Junit, Cucumber.
- Performed Debugging with Software Development Team and removed 29 code defects
- Participated in daily defect sorting and implemented to resolve defects and provided 8% contribution to system changes using JIRA tool.
- Provide timely support for production activities using fault detection and closure of tests with a 2-day TAT

EDUCATION

B.E. Bachelor of Engineering-Computer Technology

Jul 2017 - Apr 2020

Constructed IOT based Smart Wrist Band using Sensors that helped the user go online and track daily activity and health issue.

LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

• Selenium WebDriver with Java -Basics to Advanced Frameworks

Sept 2019

• Maven Crash Course

ûdemy Mar 2020

HONORS, AWARDS & APPRECIATION

• RNR Award End-to-end testing and Overall Handling of testing environment QualityKiosk Aug 2021

• Best User Acceptance Testing (UAT) Team Award ••• Atlassian

Aug 2019

